I think a positive home environment,
just, it just can make all the difference.
You know, I mean, if I think of a young
person that I worked with, who, who
came to me with quite crippling anxiety
really, but mum and dad were very present.
They were bringing him to his sessions.
They were doing some of the
work that I sent him away with.
They were together, very happy
family by the sounds of things.
And I think he was able to recover
so quickly just by taking on
the information that I gave him
and sharing it with his family.
He was -  he just changed so much in
six weeks because I think it wasn't
only the sessions that were helping him.
He then had that outside.
And I think within that positive sort of
reinforcement at home and that sense of
sort of togetherness -  and it's really
hard because so many families can't be
together - and so many of the families,
you know, the majority of the young
people that I support, there is some
sort of issues at home, I would say.
So it's rare  that we see ones where
everything's really positive, positive
at home, even if there's just one
parent at home and you've got really
good trusting relationship with them.
I think it can be the difference.
One of the biggest things about having
a positive situation at home is that
when you finish your support with a
mental health worker, it doesn't stop,
in a way, because parents are very
invested and there's stability at home.
So I think, you know, they can continue
if they feel they can continue to
talk about what's going on for them.
You know, this young person I was talking
about it, for example, if he can then
say six weeks after our sessions finished
that "oh feeling anxious again", then
his mum and dad can sort of return
him to the work he did with me without
having to refer him for more support.
So, yeah, I think it's...
it doesn't mean that you can't have
those results in someone whose life
is a bit less stable, but I think it's
a really good sort of starting block
if you've got that stability at home.